Is the beef too far with certain people to totally squash?
一部の人との因縁って
もう完全には水に流せない感じ？
Because you said you don't want beef with nobody, right?
誰とも揉めたくないって言ってたじゃん
Is it too far to say, you know what? Let's end it right here.
「もうここで終わりにしよう」って
言えないくらいこじれてんの？
We all making money. We all going our own way.
みんな稼いでるし
それぞれの道を行ってんだから
We all got our own crew.
みんな自分のクルーもいるしさ
Pull me up on it. Pull me up on it. I ain't tripping.
乗るよ、全然乗るよ
俺は気にしてねぇし
I ain't got no beef with, I don't want, now I'm not going to say I don't got,
誰とも揉めて…揉めたくねぇ
いや、揉めてないとは言わねぇけど
because I don't know how anybody looks at me,
周りが俺をどう見てるか
わかんねぇからさ
you know what I'm saying? I don't know how everybody looks at me.
わかるだろ？みんなが俺を
どう思ってるかなんてさ
Because the first beef, they say you and A Boogie, but y'all do so much.
最初の因縁はA Boogieとって
言われてるけど、2人とも大活躍じゃん
Y'all so big for New York.
ニューヨークのデカい存在なんだし
Boom.
ほらな
Tell A Boogie to come give me a hug.
A Boogieにハグしに来いって言っといて
I ain't tripping on that s**t, man.
そんなの気にしてねぇよ
Offset, I love that. What about Offset?
いいね。じゃあOffsetは？
Offset, I'm not tripping on Offset. Offset, you know what's crazy?
Offsetも気にしてねぇよ
Offsetはさ、ヤバいのが
Offset, Offset, I don't know what's up with Offset.
Offsetは…
あいつどうなってんのか知らねぇわ
Offset just need to come give me a hug, too, man. I ain't.
Offsetもハグしに来りゃいいんだよ
Now, was that over a gambling thing?
で、それってギャンブル絡みなの？
Nothing happened with us.
俺らの間には何もなかったよ
I think that my lawyer got to figure that s**t out, right?
それは弁護士が
片付けることだと思うわ
My lawyer told me so.
弁護士にそう言われてんだよ
Now, I'm not even talking about that.
いや、その話じゃなくて
I'm just talking about why y'all don't like each other.
なんで2人が仲悪いのかって話よ
Was that over a gambling thing?
ギャンブルが原因なの？
I think that, yeah, I mean, I think that a lot of people don't like Offset
まぁ、Offsetを嫌ってる奴は
多いと思うよ
because he has some gambling problems.
あいつギャンブルの問題抱えてるから
Me, I wouldn't even say I don't like him.
俺は別に
嫌いってわけじゃねぇ
I would say I kind of feel bad for him. He's kind of f**ked up.
むしろちょっと気の毒に思うわ
あいつ結構ヤバい状態だし
I kind of see what's going on, you feel me?
何が起きてんのか
見えてんのよ
I see it clear as day, you know?
はっきりとな
And I also look at him, like, you're supposed to be,
それにあいつ見てると
本来なら俺より
like, a more established, mature,
実績もあって、大人で
in this space artist than me, you feel me?
この業界でちゃんとした
アーティストのはずじゃん
And I look at how I maneuver, like, my security.
で、俺は自分の立ち回りとか
セキュリティとか見てて
I look at everything, kind of, like, everything.
全部見てんのよ、全部
I can see with my own two eyes.
自分のこの目でな
And then when we run into each other, like, I realize,
で、実際に会った時に気づくんだよ
I'm like, bro, you ain't moving like that.
「お前、全然ちゃんと
してねぇじゃん」って
God, bro, this s**t look, like, a little sad, you know what I mean?
マジでさ、ちょっと
悲しく見えんだよな